Guide to the David L. Call papers, 1977-1995.
Call, David L. papers, 1977-1995
- Outgoing correspondence, January - June 1990 (Box 67, Folder 5)
- Outgoing correspondence, July - December 1990 (Box 67, Folder 6)
- Outgoing correspondence, January - June 1991 (Box 67, Folder 7)
- Outgoing correspondence, July - December 1991 (Box 67, Folder 8)
- Outgoing correspondence, January - June 1992 (Box 67, Folder 9)
- Outgoing correspondence, July - December 1992 (Box 67, Folder 10)
- Outgoing correspondence, January - August 1993 (Box 67, Folder 11)
- Outgoing correspondence, September - December 1993 (Box 67, Folder 12)
- Mater Farmers of America, November 8, 1938 (Box 68, Folder 1)
  Includes and list of Master Farmers in New York State from the Master Farmers of America.
- Photographs (Box 68, Folder 2)
  Includes images of former Taiwan President Lee Teng-hui, Richard Lockwood, Mario Cuomo, Hank Dullea, William Parment, and others.
- China trip correspondence, March 1980 (Box 68, Folder 3)
  Information regarding 1980 Cornell delegation trip to China and Call's letters home.
- Recognitions (Box 68, Folder 4)
  Includes Marquis Who's Who, Cornell University Council, Liberty Hyde Bailey Leadership Society also a poem from Robert C. Woodbury.
- Retirement party photo album, 1995 (Box 68)
- Your Evening At The Crown Jewel Of The College, June 7, 1995 (Box 68)
  Photo album of retirement event at the New York State Agricultural Experiment Station, Geneva.
- Reflections, Volume I, June 10, 1995 (Box 68)
  Testimonials, letters, and other thanks and reminisces in recognition of Dean Call's retirement from his friends and colleagues.
- Reflections, Volume II, June 10, 1995 (Box 68)
  Testimonials, letters, and other thanks and reminisces, in recognition of Dean Call's retirement from his friends and colleagues.
- Howard Babcock Unimal Toy (wooden frame removed), Unimal coffee mug with Agway tag, and a Unimal advertisement, MU-1741-1742 (Box 69)
- Chinese vase presented to Call by President Lee Teng-hui of Taiwan., 1995; MU-1743
SEPARATED MATERIAL
Correspondence with George A. West regarding Theta Alpha fraternity, Cornell Beta Chapter, including a list of early members added to the Theta Alpha collection, #37-4-2196. Biographical information, articles, and a photograph added to faculty biographical file, #47-10-3394.